import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

Color primaryblack = Color(0xFF1A237E);

class DataSource{
  static String quote = 'Nothing in life is to be feared, it is only to be '
      'understood. Now is the time to understand more, so that we may fear less.';

  static String quotear = 'لا شيء في الحياة يُخشى ، إنه فقط ليكون '
  'يفهم. حان الوقت الآن لفهم المزيد ، حتى نخاف أقل.';

  static List questionAnswers = [
    {
      "question":'What are key facts about the global COVID-19 pandemic in '
          'the U.S.',

      "answer":'Public health measures and basic hygiene help prevent COVID-19 infection and spread'
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the signs/symptoms of COVID-19 and when do they "
          "appear?",

      "answer":
      "Common COVID-19 symptoms include fever, dry cough, fatigue, and shortness of breath."
    },
    {
      "question" : "Does COVID-19 affect children and adults differently?",

      "answer" :
      "Youth appears to offer some protection from severe COVID-19 illness."
    },
    {
      "question" : "What about pregnant women and COVID-19?",

      "answer" :
      "Experts believe pregnancy does not increase risk for acquiring "
          "COVID-19 or developing severe symptoms."
    },
    {
      "question" : ". Can pets and livestock be infected with COVID19?",

      "answer" :
      "The virus that causes COVID-19 can cause infections in animals"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How is COVID-19 different from the flu and the common cold?",

      "answer" :
      "COVID-19 spreads faster and can be more severe and deadly than influenza or the common cold"
    },
    {
      "question" : "How deadly is COVID-19?",

      "answer" :
      "COVID-19 is deadly with wide variation in fatality rates."
    },
    {
      "question" : "What is the difference between COVID-19 and the common "
          "cold? ",

      "answer" :
      "1.The common cold is caused by a different strain of coronavirus than "
          "COVID-19. /n 2.COVID-19 can be more dangerous than the common cold. "
    },
  ];

  static List questionAnswersar = [
    {
      "question":'ما هي الحقائق الرئيسية حول جائحة COVID-19 العالمي في '
          'الولايات المتحدة.',

      "answer":'تساعد تدابير الصحة العامة والنظافة الأساسية في منع انتشار عدوى COVID-19 وانتشارها'
    },
    {
      "question": "ما هي علامات / أعراض COVID-19 ومتى يحدث ذلك "
          "يظهر؟",

      "answer":
      "تشمل الأعراض الشائعة لـ COVID-19 الحمى والسعال الجاف والتعب وضيق التنفس."
    },
    {
      "question" : "هل يؤثر مرض كوفيد -19 على الأطفال والبالغين بشكل مختلف؟",

      "answer" :
      "يبدو أن الشباب يوفرون بعض الحماية من مرض COVID-19 الحاد."
    },
    {
      "question" : "ماذا عن النساء الحوامل و COVID-19؟",

      "answer" :
      "يعتقد الخبراء أن الحمل لا يزيد من خطر الإصابة "
          "COVID-19 أو ظهور أعراض شديدة."
    },
    {
      "question" : "هل يمكن أن تصاب الحيوانات الأليفة والماشية بـ COVID19؟",

      "answer" :
      "يمكن للفيروس المسبب لـ COVID-19 أن يسبب عدوى للحيوانات"
    },
    {
      "question" : "كيف يختلف COVID-19 عن الأنفلونزا ونزلات البرد؟",

      "answer" :
      "ينتشر COVID-19 بشكل أسرع ويمكن أن يكون أكثر خطورة وفتكًا من الأنفلونزا أو نزلات البرد"
    },
    {
      "question" : "ما مدى خطورة مرض كوفيد -19؟",

      "answer" :
      "كوفيد -19 قاتل مع تباين كبير في معدلات الوفيات."
    },
    {
      "question" : "ما هو الفرق بين COVID-19 والشائع؟"
      "البرد ",

      "answer" :
      "1- سبب نزلات البرد سلالة مختلفة من فيروس كورونا عن "
          "COVID-19. / n 2. COVID-19 يمكن أن يكون أكثر خطورة من نزلات البرد. "
    },
  ];
}